Guide to the James and Margaret Goff Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings and Translations, Series II
  - Other Documentation Services
    - LADOC, 1970 Jun-1973 Feb (Box 12, Folder 191)
    - Reflexion-Dialogo, Vol. 1, No. 1-3, 1971 Sep-1972 Jun (Box 12, Folder 192)
    - Servicio Colombiano de Comunicación Social (formerly Teología de La Liberación), No. 1-8, 1971 Oct-1972 May (Box 12, Folder 193)
    - Teología de La Liberación Documentación (later S.C.C.S.), No. 1-9, 1970 Apr-Dec (Box 12, Folder 194)
    - Teología de La Liberación Documentación, No. 10-18, 1971 Jan-Sep (Box 12, Folder 195)
    - World Council of Churches (WCC), Documentation Service on Development Information Sheets 1-8, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - WCC Documentation Service on Development Information Sheets 1-5, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - WCC Documentation Service on Development Catalogue, 1970 Oct 31 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - WCC Documentation Service on Development Catalogues, 1971 Jan 31, 1971 Mar 31 (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - WCC Documentation Service on Development Catalogue, 1972 Jun 30 (Box 12, Folder 200)
- Correspondence, Series III
  - Family, U.S. Churches
    - Family, 1962 Jun-1973 (Box 12, Folder 201-203)
    - Family, 1983, 1985, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 204)
    - U.S. Churches, B-C, 1956-70 (Box 13, Folder 205)
    - U.S. Churches, F, 1953-70 (Box 13, Folder 206)
    - U.S. Churches, H-R, 1959-85 (Box 13, Folder 207)
    - U.S. Churches, S-W, 1953-72 (Box 13, Folder 208)
    - U.S. Churches/Supporters Misc., 1956-62 (Box 13, Folder 209)
  - General Correspondence
    - Appointment to Colombia, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 210)
    - Misc., 1950-1967 (Box 13, Folder 211-212)
    - John H. Sinclair, 1963-67 (Box 13, Folder 213)
    - Personal Issues (Presbyterian Church of Colombia), 1964-69 (Box 13, Folder 214)
    - Donald Black, 1967-71 (Box 13, Folder 215)
    - Misc., 1968-1969 Jun (Box 13, Folder 216-217)
    - Misc., 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 13a, Folder 218)
    - Latin American Evangelist Magazine, 1968 Apr-1969 Nov (Box 13a, Folder 219)
    - Transfer to Mexico, 1969-70 (Box 13a, Folder 220)
    - Misc., 1970 (Box 13a, Folder 221-222)
    - United Presbyterian Foundation, 1970-71 (Box 13a, Folder 223)
    - Re:/To: President Nixon, 1970-72 (Box 13a, Folder 224)
    - Misc., 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 13a, Folder 225)
    - Misc., 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 14, Folder 226)
    - Unfinished Letters, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 227)
    - Re: Wilbur Kuhl, 1971 Apr-1972 Nov (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - Wilbur Kuhl Background Material, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    - Misc., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - Re: Church World Service, 1972 Oct 26-1973 Jun 3 (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - A.D. Magazine, 1972 Oct 27-1973 Apr 3 (Box 14, Folder 232)
    - Misc., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - Re: Emerging Economies Corporation, 1978 Feb 16-1978 Nov 27 (Box 14, Folder 234)
    - Emerging Economies Corp. (Background Material), 1977-78 (Box 14, Folder 235)
    - Misc., 1978-1987 (Box 14, Folder 236-241)
    - Jose Maria Vigil re. articles by Leonel Saavedra, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 894)
    - Misc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 242)
    - Presbyterians for Democracy and Religious Freedom (Paul Scotchmer), 1989 Jun 14-Jul 18 (Box 14, Folder 243)
    - JG to Avila and Kalke re. translation work for Amanecer, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 895)
    - Misc., incl. letters to editors, 1990 - 1995 (Box 46a, Folder 874)
  - Missionary Circulars
    - Misc., 1957-71 (Box 14, Folder 244)
    - Misc., 1987-96 (Box 15, Folder 245)
    - Campbell, 1988-99 (Box 15, Folder 246)
    - Cantera, 1990-92 (Box 15, Folder 247)
    - Central American Education Program-Stony Point, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 248-249)
    - Cookson, 1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 250)
    - Collier/Garber, 1990-98 (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - Glenn, 1990-93 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Hale, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - Kinsler, 1987-2000 (Box 15, Folder 254)
    - Koll, 1989-97 (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - Lausch, 1989-94 (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - Pierce, Jeffrey, 1990-98 (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - Pixley, 1990-92 (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - Smith, 1989-99 (Box 15, Folder 259)
    - Tabor House, 1990-96 (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - Wessel, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - Wheaton, 1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 262)
- Sermons and Talks, Series IV
  - Sermons/Prayers
    - Sermons/Prayers, 1953 Jul-1960 (Box 15, Folder 263-269)
    - Sermons/Prayers, 1961-2003, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 270-276)
    - Holy Week (Box 16, Folder 277)
    - Good Friday (Box 16, Folder 278)
    - Easter (Box 16, Folder 279)
  - Talks/Interviews/Lectures
    - Radio Interview:Samuel Nelson, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 280)
    - Radio Interview:Latin American Mission, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 281)
    - Religious Life in Latin America Council of Mennonite Colleges Lectures, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 282)
    - Religious Life in Latin America Correspondence/Misc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 283)
    - Central America Week, 1991 Mar (Box 16, Folder 284)
    - Quincentenial Talks, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 285-287)
    - A Slum Called Hope: Talk by MPG., 1994 Apr 22 (Box 16, Folder 288)
    - Miscellaneous notes for talks - 5" x8" notebook sheets (Box 48, Folder 896)
- Activities, Series V
  - Minutes/documents of CEDEC and Presbyterian Church in Colombia
    - CEDEC, 1954, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 289)
    - CEDEC, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 290-292)
    - Constitución de La Iglesia Presbiteriana de Colombia, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 293)
    - Iglesia Presbiteriana de Colombia, 1962 Mar-1969 Jul (Box 17, Folder 294-297)
    - Iglesia Presbiteriana de Colombia Consultation, 1968 Jun 28 (Box 17, Folder 298)
    - Comisión Sinodica de Educación Iglesia Presbiteriana en Colombia, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 299-300)
    - Comisión del Noroeste Colombiano Iglesia Presbiteriana, 1967-68 (Box 17, Folder 301)
    - Iglesia Presbiteriana de Colombia Misc. (Box 17, Folder 302)
    - Presbiterio Central, 1962 Apr-1968 Dec (Box 17, Folder 303-304)
  - CEDEC Census
    - Colombia: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 305)
    - Colombia: Tally Sheet, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 306)
    - Colombia: 1. C+MA, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 307)
    - Colombia: 2. Assemblies of God, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 308)
    - Colombia: 3. Misión Evangélica, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 309)
    - Colombia: 4. Cumberland Presbyterian, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 310)
    - Colombia: 5. Lutheran World Federation, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 311)
    - Colombia: 6. Brethren, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 312)
    - Colombia: 7. I.C. del Norte, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 313)
    - Colombia: 8. Lutheran Church, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 314)
    - Colombia: 9. Iglesia de Dios, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 315)
    - Colombia: 10. Cuadrangular, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 316)
    - Colombia: 11. Sociedad Misionera Interamericana, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 317)
    - Colombia: 12. Iglesia Evangélica Cristiana Libreria Moderna, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 318)
    - Colombia: 13. Hermanos Menonitas, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 319)
    - Colombia: 14. Misión Bautista de Colombia, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 320)
    - Colombia: 16. Mennonite, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 322)
    - Colombia: 17. LAM, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 323)
    - Colombia: 18. Wesleyan Methodist, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 324)
    - Colombia: 19. Misión Panamamericana, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 325)
    - Colombia: 20. Embajadoros, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 326)
    - Colombia: 21. Presbiteriana, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 327)
    - Colombia: 22. South American Indian Mission, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 328)
    - Colombia: 24. Bible Society, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 329)
    - Colombia: 25. Team, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 330)
    - Colombia: 26. Gospel Missionary Union, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 331)
    - Colombia: 27. Union Evangélica de America del Sur, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 332)
    - Colombia: 28. W.E.C., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 333)
    - Colombia: 29. 7th-Day Adventist, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 334)
    - Colombia: 30. United Pentecostal, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 335)
    - Colombia: 31. Leticia Baptist, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 336)
    - Colombia: 32. Episcopal, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 337)
    - Colombia: 33. Wycliffe Translators, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 338)
    - Colombia: 34. New Tribes Mission, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 339)
    - Colombia: 35. Misiones Mundiales, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 340)
    - Colombia: 36. Union Church, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 341)
    - Colombia: 37. Casa de Oración, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 342)
    - Colombia: 39: Asociacion Nacional de Iglesias Cristianas, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 343)
    - Colombia: 40. Iglesia Cristiana Pentecostes, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 344)
    - Colombia: 41. Cruzada Hispanoamericana, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 345)
    - Colombia: 43. Quakers, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 346)
    - Colombia: 44. Iglesia de Dios Pentecostal, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 347)
    - Colombia: 45. Independent, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 348)
    - Colombia: Misc., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 349)
    - Colombia: Tally Sheet, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 350)
    - Colombia: 1. C+MA, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 351)
    - Colombia: 2. Assemblies of God, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 352)
    - Colombia: 3. Misión Evangélica, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 353)
    - Colombia: 4. Cumberland Pres., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 354)
    - Colombia: 5. Lutheran World Federation, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 355)
    - Colombia: 6. Brethren, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 356)
    - Colombia: 7. Iglesia Cristiana del Norte, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 357)
    - Colombia: 8. Lutheran, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 358)
    - Colombia: 9. Iglesia de Dios, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 359)
    - Colombia: 10. Cuadrangular, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - Colombia: 11. Interamerican, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 361)
    - Colombia: 12. Iglesia Evangélica Cristiana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 362)
    - Colombia: 13. Hermanos Menonitas, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 363)
    - Colombia: 14. Convención Bautista, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 364)
    - Colombia: 15. Misión Bautista Fundamental del Canada, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - Colombia: 16. Mennonite Mission, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 366)
    - Colombia: 17. LAM, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 367)
    - Colombia: 18. Metodista Wesleyana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 368)
    - Colombia: 19. Misión Panamericana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 369)
    - Colombia: 20. Embajadores, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 370)
    - Colombia: 21. Presbiteriana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 371)
    - Colombia: 22. South American Indian Mission, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 372)
    - Colombia: 23. SEPAL, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 373)
    - Colombia: 25. Misión Alianza Evangélica, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 374)
    - Colombia: 26. Union Misionara Evangélica, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 375)
    - Colombia: 27. Union Evangélica de America del Sur, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 376)
    - Colombia: 28. Worldwide Evangelization Crusade, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 377)
    - Colombia: 29. Adventist, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 378)
    - Colombia: 30. United Pentecostal, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 379)
    - Colombia: 31. Leticia Baptist, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 380)
    - Colombia: 32. Episcopal, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 381)
    - Colombia: 34. New Tribes, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 382)
    - Colombia: 35. Mundiales, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 383)
    - Colombia: 36. Union Church, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 384)
    - Colombia: 37. Casa de Oración, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 385)
    - Colombia: 39. Assoc. Nal. de Iglesia Cristiana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 386)
    - Colombia: 41. Cruzada Hispanoamericana, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 387)
    - Colombia: 43. Quakers, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 388)
    - Colombia: 44. Iglesia de Dios Pentecostal, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 389)
    - Colombia: 46. Closed Plymouth Brethren, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 390)
    - Colombia: 47. Misión Cristiana La Fe, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 391)
    - Colombia: 48. Iglesia Evangélica La Hermosa, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 392)
    - Colombia: 49. Iglesia Evangélica Elim, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 393)
    - Colombia, 1968-69 (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - Colombia: Comprehensive Report, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - Venezuela: 1. Anglican-Caracas, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 396)
    - Venezuela: 2. Assemblies of God, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - Venezuela: 3. Nacional Bautista, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - Venezuela: 4. Bethel, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 399)
    - Venezuela: 5. Emmaus, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Venezuela: 6. Iglesia Evangélica de Puerto Ordaz, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 401)
    - Venezuela: Lutheran, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 402)
    - Venezuela: Iglesia Evangélica Nativa de Apure, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 403)
    - Venezuela: Iglesia Evangélica de Occ. y Sur, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - Venezuela: Iglesia de Dios Pentecostal, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 405)
    - Venezuela: Presbiteriana, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 406)
    - Venezuela: 7th-Day Adventist, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 407)
    - Venezuela: Union Church of Eastern Ven., 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 408)
    - Venezuela: United Christian Church, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 409)
    - Venezuela: Misión Mundo Unido, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 410)
    - Venezuela: Mundial, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 411)
    - Venezuela: Bible Society, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 412)
    - Venezuela: Southern Baptist, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 413)
    - Venezuela: Iglesia Evangélica Libre de Ven., 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 414)
    - Venezuela: LWF, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 415)
    - Venezuela: Buen Samarito, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 416)
    - Venezuela: Independent, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 417)
    - Venezuela: Iglesia Evangélica Los Acacias, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 418)
  - Crisis in the Nation Redeployment
    - J.E.G. Itinerary, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 419)
    - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 420)
    - Hispanic Americans Report (Box 20, Folder 421)
    - Hispanic Americans-Notes (Box 20, Folder 422)
    - Redeployment Team Report (Synod of Southern California) (Box 20, Folder 423)
    - Chicano Legal Defense-Notes/Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 424)
    - Chicano Legal Defense-General Documentation (Box 20, Folder 425)
    - Chicano Legal Defense-East L.A. School Walk-Outs (Box 20, Folder 426)
    - Calvary Presbyterian, San Diego (Box 20, Folder 427)
    - Civil Disorders (Box 20, Folder 428)
    - Crisis Report Newsletter (Box 20, Folder 429)
    - Detroit Redeployment Team (Box 20, Folder 430)
    - Greater Parish Ministry-San Diego (Box 20, Folder 431)
    - Interfaith Efforts (Box 20, Folder 432)
    - Low-Income Housing (Box 20, Folder 433)
    - Background Mexican-American Education (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - Spanish-American Work (Box 20a, Folder 435)
    - Synod of Southern California (Box 20a, Folder 436)
    - UPCUSA Statements (Box 20a, Folder 437)
    - White Racism (Box 20a, Folder 438)
    - Misc. (Box 20a, Folder 439)
  - Other Studies and Ministries from Colombia Era
    - Research Tour on Religious Liberty, Notes of Interviews, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 440)
    - Pastors Compensation Study-Final Report, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 441)
    - Pastors Compensation Study-Surveys and Notes, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 442)
    - Pastors Pensions Study-Reports, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 443)
    - Pastors Pensions Study-Notes, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 444)
    - Pastors Pensions Study-Correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 21, Folder 445)
    - Pastors Pensions Study-Surveys, 1967-68 (Box 21, Folder 446)
    - Mimeographed notes on preparing sermons and evangelism, ca.1967 (Box 48, Folder 897)
    - J. Goff Notes, Religion in Latin America, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 447-448)
    - Notes/ Drafts-J.E.G. Persecution in Colombia, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 449)
    - J. Goff Notes Misc., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 450)
    - J Goff note cards, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 880)
    - Notes re. Boren's three laws, Max Weber, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 881)
    - Notes re. Docetismo, Gnosticismo, Apologistas, etc., n.d. (Box 47, Folder 882)
    - Notes on Why Church against Revolution?, Bishop's idea of change, The Church in LA, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 883)
    - M.P.G notes in Spanish, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 884)
    - Interviews by J. Goff with Preman Niles and nalini Jayasuriya (Box 47, Folder 885)
    - M.P.G.-Notes, Church/Mission in Colombia, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 451)
    - Biographical Notes-M.P.G. Colombia Mission, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 452)
    - Publicity Committee Colombia Mission, M.P.G.-Chair, 1954-56 (Box 21, Folder 453)
    - Union Church, Barranquilla, 1954, 1958-67 (Box 21, Folder 454)
    - Credos (in Spanish) Barranquilla, Colombia, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 455)
    - Christian Education Notes, Etc.-M.P.G., 1957, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 456)
    - Women's Ministries Presbyterian Church of Colombia-M.P.G., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 457)
    - Alfabetización-M.P.G., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 458)
    - Colegio Americano Bogota, J.E.G.-Principal, 1964-66 (Box 21, Folder 459)
    - Palmero Church General Documents, 1965-67 (Box 21, Folder 460)
    - Palmero Church Orders of Service, 1967-68 (Box 21, Folder 461)
    - Palmero Church Pastoral Letters, 1966-68 (Box 21, Folder 462)
    - Palmero Church Correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 21, Folder 463)
    - Palmero Church Note Cards (Box 21, Folder 464)
  - Theological Community
    - Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 22, Folder 465)
    - Bibliography, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 466)
    - Studies and Papers, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 467)
    - Collected Curricula (Box 22, Folder 468-470)
    - Cuernavaca, Mex. (J. Sinclair, Organizer), 1969 Aug 3-16 (Box 22, Folder 471)
    - Cuernavaca, Mex. (General Documentation), 1970 Jan 25-Feb 7 (Box 22, Folder 472)
    - Cuernavaca, Mex. (Correspondence), 1970 Jan 25-Feb 2 (Box 22, Folder 473)
    - Cuernavaca-Cancelled, 1970 Aug 2-15 (Box 22, Folder 474)
    - Austin, TX, U.S.A., 1971 Jan 2-9 (Box 22, Folder 475)
    - Bogotá, Col. (General Documentation), 1971 Feb 14-27 (Box 22, Folder 476)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Notes-J.E.G.), 1971 Feb 14-27 (Box 22, Folder 477)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Evaluations), 1971 Feb 14-27 (Box 22, Folder 478)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Press Releases/CEDEC Minutes), 1971 Feb 14-27 (Box 22, Folder 479)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Press Coverage), 1971 Feb 14-27 (Box 22, Folder 480)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Correspondence), 1971 Feb 14-27, Apr-May (Box 22, Folder 481)
    - Bogotá, Col. (Correspondence), 1971 Feb 14-27, Jun-Jul (Box 22, Folder 482)
  - LAWG Seminars
    - Mexico City, General Documentation, 1972 Aug 6-18 (Box 23, Folder 483)
    - Mexico City, Conference Notebook, p.1, 1972 Aug 6-18 (Box 23, Folder 484)
    - Mexico City, Conference Notebook, p.2, 1972 Aug 6-18 (Box 23, Folder 485)
    - Mexico City, Correspondence, 1972 Aug 6-18, Jan-Jun (Box 23, Folder 486)
    - Mexico City, Correspondence, 1972 Aug 6-18, Jul-Sep (Box 23, Folder 487)
    - Mexico City, Notes/ Receipts, 1972 Aug 6-18 (Box 23, Folder 488)
    - Buenos Aires, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 489)
  - WCCE Encuentros
    - General Documents, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 490)
    - WCCE Encuentros - General Documents, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 898)
    - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 491)
    - Background, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 492)
    - Argentina, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 493)
    - Bolivia, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 494)
    - Brazil, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 495)
    - Chile, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 496)
    - Colombia, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 497)
    - Costa Rica/Panama, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 498)
    - Cuba, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 499)
    - Dominican Republic, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 500)
    - Dominican Republic, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 501)
    - Ecuador, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 502-503)
    - El Salvador, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 504-507)
    - Guatemala, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 508)
    - Haiti, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 509-510)
    - Jamaica, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 511-512)
    - Mexico, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 513)
    - Paraguay, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 515)
  - Other Activities from Mexico Era, Nicaragua Friendship Project
    - Brazil-Human Rights Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 25, Folder 516)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Distribution (Box 25, Folder 517)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Correspondence, Ben Rose, PCUS, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 518)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Latin American Dept., NCC Response, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 519)
    - Brazil-Human Rights CCIA/WCC Response, 1970-71 (Box 25, Folder 520)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Related Documents, 1970-71 (Box 25, Folder 521)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Related Documents Misc., 1970, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 522)
    - Brazil-Human Rights Related Documents, Terror in Brazil: A Dossier, 1970 Apr (Box 25, Folder 523)
    - Colombia-Human Rights Correspondence, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 524)
    - Sodepax Bibliography, J.E.G.- Contributor (Correspondence), 1969-70 (Box 25, Folder 525)
    - J.E.G.-Notes on La Live, El Refugio de Las Masas, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 526)
    - J. Goff Notes Misc., 1969-70 (Box 25, Folder 527)
    - J.E.G. Notes, U.S. Foreign Affairs, 1972-73 (Box 25, Folder 528)
    - Muskingum College Study Tour, 1970 Jan 11-28 (Box 25, Folder 529)
    - A Problem of Power Film, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 530)
    - Minutes, 1970-72 (Box 25, Folder 531)
    - Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 25, Folder 532)
    - Working Party I (Box 25, Folder 533)
    - Working Parties II-IV (Box 25, Folder 534)
    - Appendix A (Box 25, Folder 535)
    - Appendix C (Box 25, Folder 536)
    - Background Materials (Box 25, Folder 537)
    - World Christian Handbook, J.E.G.-Associate Editor, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 538)
    - Readings on the Church and Social Change, Mexico City Mission Station Cover Sheets, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 539)
  - Retirement Activities
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Project Correspondence, 1987-92 (Box 25, Folder 540)
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Quilali Water Project, 1989-93 (Box 26, Folder 541)
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Prodecoop Correspondence, 1991-94 (Box 26, Folder 542)
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Project Public Events, 1990-95 (Box 26, Folder 543)
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Project Background, 1989-91 (Box 26, Folder 544)
    - Nicaragua-Ponoma Valley Friendship Project Background, 1992-94 (Box 26, Folder 545)
    - Nicaragua Election Watch (General Documents), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 546)
    - Nicaragua Election Watch (Notes-J.E.G.), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 547)
    - Habitat for Humanity, Pomona valley, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 899)
    - Siloe Church/Carlos Escorcia, 1990 Aug-1991 Aug (Box 26, Folder 549)
    - Siloe Church/Carlos Escorcia, 1991 Sep (Box 26, Folder 550)
    - Siloe Church/Carlos Escorcia, 1991 Oct-1992 Jan (Box 26, Folder 551)
    - Siloe Church/Carlos Escorcia Notes (Box 26, Folder 552)
    - El Salvador/Ponoma Valley Council of Churches, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 553)
    - Ernesto Cardenal Poetry Reading, 1990 Nov 15 (Box 26, Folder 554)
    - Nicaragua Research Seminar Participant List, 1991 Jun 15-28 (Box 26, Folder 555)
    - U.S.-Cuba Friendship Assoc., 1992-93 (Box 26, Folder 556)
    - U.S.-Cuba Friendshipment, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 557)
    - U.S.-Cuba Friendshipment, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 558)
    - Leadership Summit on Cuba, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 559)
    - U.S.-Cuba Friendshipment, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 560)
    - Hudson River Presbtery Peace Action Working Group, 1988-89 (Box 27, Folder 561)
    - Rigoberta Menchu Attempted Speaking Engagement, 1992-93 (Box 27, Folder 562)
    - International Plebiscite on Chiapas, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 563)
    - One Million Women Campaign, Seminario Biblico Latinoamericano, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 564)
    - Task Force on Central America and the Caribbean Claremont United Church of Christ, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 900)
    - Religious working group on the World Bank and the IMF, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 901)
    - Charles Goff, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 565)
    - Flora Guerrero Goff, 1991, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 566)
    - Fred Goff, 1972, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 567)
- Collected Material, Series VI
  - Conferences
    - First Latin Americna Presbyterian Conference, Capinas Brazil, 1955 Jul (Box 27, Folder 568)
    - The Pattern of Protestant Progress in Latin America (NCC), Buck Hill Falls, Penn., 1956 Nov 24-46 (Box 27, Folder 569)